https://www.demetrios.com/privacy-policy

Privacy Policy | Demetrios
Book an AppointmentUSAGermanInternational EnglishItalianSpanishUnited Kingdom Register - LoginMy Account STAR STYLES -
SearchBook an AppointmentUSAGermanInternational EnglishItalianSpanishUnited KingdomWEDDING DRESSESCOLLECTIONSDEMETRIOS COLLECTIONPLATINUM BY DEMETRIOSDESTINATION ROMANCECOSMOBELLA COLLECTIONMETROPOLITAN COLLECTIONOREASPOSA COLLECTIONSTYLEPRINCESSCLASSIC/SIMPLEROMANTICBOHOGLAMTRENDSPRINCESS BRIDETWO PIECESSEXY BACKSVINTAGELONG TRAINSSILHOUETTESBALLGOWNA-LINEFLAREDSHEATHNECKLINE/SLEEVESWEETHEARTV-NECKILLUSIONOFF THE SHOULDERLONG SLEEVESOCCASION + ACCESSORIESEVENING DRESSESVeilsCapes & JacketsDetachable SleevesDetachable TrainsSTORESTRUNK SHOWSBLOG STAR STYLES -
MenuHOMEPAGEABOUT DEMETRIOSDEMETRIOS – THE STORYBRANDSWEDDING DRESSESCOLLECTIONSDEMETRIOS COLLECTIONPLATINUM BY DEMETRIOSDESTINATION ROMANCECOSMOBELLA COLLECTIONMETROPOLITAN COLLECTIONOREASPOSA COLLECTIONSTYLEPRINCESSCLASSIC/SIMPLEROMANTICBOHOGLAMTRENDSPRINCESS BRIDETWO PIECESSEXY BACKSVINTAGELONG TRAINSSILHOUETTESBALLGOWNA-LINEFLAREDSHEATHNECKLINE/SLEEVESWEETHEARTV-NECKILLUSIONOFF THE SHOULDERLONG SLEEVESALL COLLECTIONSOCCASION + ACCESSORIESEVENING DRESSESVeilsCapes & JacketsDetachable SleevesDetachable TrainsSTORESTRUNK SHOWSBLOGCONTACTUSAGermanInternational EnglishItalianSpanishUnited KingdomThrough our Privacy Policy, Demetrios Group (“Demetrios”) informs its users of the type of data collected, the use that will be made of this data and the user’s right of access, modification or elimination of said data.Demetrios declares that it complies with the current regulations of Personal Data Protection.Data controllerDemetrios certifies that the company Demetrios Group is responsible for the control of the data and is available to users through the email address info@Demetrios.com, as well as via postal address Via Feltre 34/7 • 20132 Milano , to discuss any queries.Personal Data we gatherAs part of the service provided, Demetrios requires the personal data of its users. Demetrios agrees to only collect the necessary data for the provision of its services and guarantees the use of all necessary means to protect said data. The mandatory data will be marked with an asterisk (*) in the corresponding forms. The rest of the non-mandatory data requested will be facilitated by the user under their responsibility and consent.The data can be collected through Demetrios’s registration forms, email, chat, phone, websites associated to social networks or fairs and/or events organized by Demetrios or third parties. In the case that the data is collected through a third party, the good use and correct application of Privacy Policy is the responsibility of said third party.The refusal to provide the data requested may result in the inability to use some parts or all of the services provided by Demetrios.The type of data collected may vary according to the type of user:Real Brides, Brides to be & RetailersFor individuals or users that are couples or guests, the following data may be collected according to the services they have subscribed to and/or used:Name and Surname.Email, phone number, address.Username on social networks.ProfessionalsName and Surname.Name of the companyEmail, phone number, address.Industry area.How we use personal dataThe personal data collected from the users will only be used in relation to the services offered by Demetrios.Help with the wedding dress or nearest store and contact with the Retailers Allow the quick and easy search of wedding stores for users who looking for a specific dressPut professionals in contact with future newly-weds who can book an appointment by requesting it via email or phone.Promote products and events through the publication of a professional tab. Through the said professional profile, all the relevant and pertinent information will be shared with couples by Province and business sector.Provide the users with high quality content in order to help them organize their wedding through editorial and advertising articles.Allow the users to be involved in the Demetrios community through the publication of public comments both in magazine articles and the files in our website and blog.During the period of time Demetrios is connected to its users or until the user withdraws consent, Demetrios reserves the right to send electronic communication related to the services and news offered by DemetriosSharing InformationDemetrios undertakes to implement all the necessary means in order to protect the user’s data and communicate this information only within the framework of legislation that governs its activity or in one of the cases explained below.Users that could be defined as brides or retailers accept the distribution of their data to companies that appear on Demetrios and in ones the user has shown interest in, especially during first contact made through the Demetrios website or during the participation in a competition organized jointly by Demetrios and one of its retailers.Professional user’s data will be communicated to third parties only in the context of connecting future retailers and brides or according to the legislation that governs Demetrios’s activity as mentioned above.User’s RightsThe user can at any time exercise their right of access to,modification and elimination of their data.The execution of these rights can be carried out directly from the subcriber’s profile, they can also in the case of doubt or technical concern get in contact with Demetrios through their postal address Via Feltre 34/7 • 20132 Milano, by email at info@demetrios.com .In the case that the user believes there has been a violation of their rights; they can send a complaint directly to Demetrios through the contact information previously stated.SecurityDemetrios informs its users that all the necessary means have been implemented, from a technological as well as organizational point of view, to guarantee the security of personal data and avoid loss, alteration or unauthorized processing.The policies of cookieshttps://www.demetrios.com/cookie-policy/ContactDemetrios provides its users with the email info@demetrios.com.
Generic selectors
Exact matches only Exact matches only
Search in title Search in title
Search in content Search in content
Search in excerpt
Search in posts Search in posts
Search in pages Search in pages
Hidden
Login Username or email address *
Password *
Remember me
Log in Lost your password?Register Email address * A password will be sent to your email address.Your personal data will be used to support your experience throughout this website, to manage access to your account, and for other purposes described in our privacy policy.
RegisterStar Styles Your Wishlist is currently empty. Return To ShopCOLLECTIONSDEMETRIOS COLLECTIONPLATINUM BY DEMETRIOSDESTINATION ROMANCECOSMOBELLA COLLECTIONMETROPOLITAN COLLECTIONOREASPOSA COLLECTIONSTYLEPRINCESSCLASSIC/SIMPLEROMANTICBOHOGLAMTRENDSPRINCESS BRIDETWO PIECESSEXY BACKSVINTAGELONG TRAINSSILHOUETTESBALLGOWNA-LINEFLAREDSHEATHNECKLINE/SLEEVESWEETHEARTV-NECKILLUSIONOFF THE SHOULDERLONG SLEEVESCOLLECTIONSDEMETRIOS COLLECTIONPLATINUM BY DEMETRIOSDESTINATION ROMANCECOSMOBELLA COLLECTIONMETROPOLITAN COLLECTIONOREASPOSA COLLECTIONSTYLEPRINCESSCLASSIC/SIMPLEROMANTICBOHOGLAMTRENDSPRINCESS BRIDETWO PIECESSEXY BACKSVINTAGELONG TRAINSSILHOUETTESBALLGOWNA-LINEFLAREDSHEATHNECKLINE/SLEEVESWEETHEARTV-NECKILLUSIONOFF THE SHOULDERLONG SLEEVESFAQBecome a RetailerPrivacy PolicyAuthentic ProductsContactCopyright © 2020 DEMETRIOS Website design & development by Horizon
MenuThis website uses cookies to provide you with the best browsing experience.Find out more or adjust your settings. Accept
Privacy Overview
Strictly Necessary Cookies
3rd Party Cookies Privacy OverviewThis website uses cookies so that we can provide you with the best user experience possible. Cookie information is stored in your browser and performs functions such as recognising you when you return to our website and helping our team to understand which sections of the website you find most interesting and useful. Strictly Necessary CookiesStrictly Necessary Cookie should be enabled at all times so that we can save your preferences for cookie settings. disable
If you disable this cookie, we will not be able to save your preferences. This means that every time you visit this website you will need to enable or disable cookies again. 3rd Party CookiesThis website uses Google Analytics to collect anonymous information such as the number of visitors to the site, and the most popular pages.Keeping this cookie enabled helps us to improve our website. disable
Please enable Strictly Necessary Cookies first so that we can save your preferences! Enable All Save Changes
